<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
~  Copyright (c) 2018, WSO2 Inc. (http://wso2.com) All Rights Reserved.
~
~  WSO2 Inc. licenses this file to you under the Apache License,
~  Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except
~  in compliance with the License.
~  You may obtain a copy of the License at
~
~   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
~
~  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
~  software distributed under the License is distributed on an
~  "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
~  KIND, either express or implied.  See the License for the
~  specific language governing permissions and limitations
~  under the License.
-->
<component name="epic-search" type="synapse/template">
    <subComponents>
        <component name="searchPatient">
            <file>searchPatient.xml</file>
            <description>Search Patient using the given parameters</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchAllergyIntolerance">
            <file>searchAllergyIntolerance.xml</file>
            <description>The AllergyIntolerance resource defines the substance that elicited the response, as well as when the reaction occured, the severity, and the type of reaction noted. </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchMedicationOrder">
            <file>searchMedicationOrder.xml</file>
            <description> The FHIR MedicationOrder resource defines detailed information about a medication that was ordered for a patient, including prescriptions or OTC drugs ordered in an ambulatory clinic. </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchMedicationStatement">
            <file>searchMedicationStatement.xml</file>
            <description> The FHIR MedicationStatement resource defines detailed information about medications being consumed by a patient, including medication prescriptions, OTC drugs ordered in an ambulatory clinic, and medications reported by a patient. </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchCondition">
            <file>searchCondition.xml</file>
            <description>The FHIR Condition resource defines detailed information about a Condition, problem, or diagnosis relevant to the health of the patient.  </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchFamilyMemberHistory">
            <file>searchFamilyMemberHistory.xml</file>
            <description>The FHIR FamilyMemberHistory resource defines a patient's family history. This resource returns the current status, age, and medical and surgical history of relatives related to a specific patient. </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchObservation">
            <file>searchObservation.xml</file>
            <description>The FHIR Observation resource defines information about a measurement or simple assertion made about a patient.  </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchDiagnosticReport">
            <file>searchDiagnosticReport.xml</file>
            <description>The FHIR DiagnosticReport resource contains information about a single diagnostic service performed for a patient.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchImmunization">
            <file>searchImmunization.xml</file>
            <description>The FHIR Immunization Resource provides information about a patient's immunizations</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchProcedure">
            <file>searchProcedure.xml</file>
            <description>The FHIR Procedure resource defines an activity performed on or with a patient as part of the provision of care</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchDocumentReference">
            <file>searchDocumentReference.xml</file>
            <description> The FHIR DocumentReference resource describes information about a document</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchCarePlan">
            <file>searchCarePlan.xml</file>
            <description> The FHIR CarePlan resource is a broad container for summarizing the plan of treatment for a patient.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchGoal">
            <file>searchGoal.xml</file>
            <description> The FHIR Goal resource defines objectives for a patient based on a current condition or recent procedure.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchDevice">
            <file>searchDevice.xml</file>
            <description> The FHIR Device resource describes information about a specific patient's durable, manufactured medical items.</description>
        </component>
    </subComponents>
</component>
